

# CEPHAS OYIWOSE OSAYI

#### **PROFILE**

An independent and self-motivated computer science graduate with interest in Data. Experience working in an IT company as frontend engineer and in a Government establishment as a desk officer. Highly analytical, motivated and skilled at solving technical problems. Can work well both independently and in a team.

### **MY SKILLS**

PROGRAMMING

WEB DESIGN

DIGITAL MARKETING AND ANALYTICS

DATA ANALYISIS

MICROSOFT OFFICE SKILLS

ORGANIZATION

COMMUNICATION

TEAMWORK

ADAPTABILITY

#### REFERENCE

**On Request** 

Lafia, Nasarawa State.

C

08077827613

in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ceph asosayi/

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

cephasosayi@gmail.com

## Front-end Developer Ullweb Technology

2021 - Present

#### **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Maintaining brand consistency throughout the design.
- Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Ensuring web design is optimized for smartphones.
- Translate UI/UX design wireframes to actual code

#### Web Designer Easydrop Web Services

2020- 2021

#### **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- · Develop new user facing features
- Translate UI/UX design wireframes to actual code

#### Desk Officer

#### **Board of Internal Revenue Nasarawa State**

2019- 2021

#### **Key Qualifications & Responsibilities**

- Data Collection
- Tax Processing officer
- Payment invoice generation and payments.

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

## **B.sc Computer Science**

2016 - 2021

#### Federal University Lafia

- Gained extensive training and successfully accomplished all courses for computer sciences
- Graduated with a second class honour degree

#### Front-end Career Path

Google/Andela Scholarship

2018

## **Digital Marketing**

Google Garage

2019

## Data Analyst

Codecademy Micro COurse

2019